http://www.cl.cam.ac.uk/privacy.html

Email & phone search
Computer LaboratoryWeb server privacy policyDepartment of Computer Science and TechnologyComputer LaboratoryHomeThe departmentOverviewPeopleOverviewAcademic staffSupport staffContract researchersFellows & affiliatesPhD studentsVisitorsSeminarsOverviewWednesday Seminar SeriesWheeler Lectureswomen@cl 10th AnniversaryComputer Laboratory 75th AnniversaryHistoryFacilitiesOverviewReceptionFoodShopping and leisureCyclingLibraryOverview[no title found]Library guidesCataloguesCoronavirus resourcesElectronic resourcesLocal servicesLab technical reportsExternal technical reportsResource listsReading listsReprographics equipmentArchivesMaps and directionsContact informationResearchOverviewArtificial IntelligenceOverviewPeopleGroup MeetingsProject ideas for current studentsComputer ArchitectureOverviewProjects and research topicsACS & Part II/III Project SuggestionsPeopleSelected PublicationsOpen source componentsGroup MeetingsContact DetailsDigital TechnologyGraphics & InteractionOverviewResearchMembersProjectsApplying to do a PhDProject suggestionsOther informationNatural Language ProcessingOverviewPeoplePublicationsProjectsPostgraduate opportunitiesResourcesProgramming, Logic, SemanticsSecurityOverviewPeoplePublicationsProjects and topicsSecurity Seminar SeriesMeetingsCoursesPostersJournalsMailing listsblogSystemsOverviewResearch ProjectsMembersSeminarsStudent ProjectsResearch supportOverviewResearch grantsFellowshipsMeetings & TravelIndustrial CollaborationCommercialisationWriting a proposalImpact statementsCollaborating with the Computer LabMaking your work publicAdmissionsOverviewUndergraduate Computer Science at CambridgeOverviewCourseOpen DaysApplyCSATFAQContactMPhil ACSOverviewModulesPhD applicationsResearchGraduate Admissions ProspectusFunding deadlinesPhD degreeOverviewResearchGraduate Admissions ProspectusFunding deadlinesMPhil in Advanced Computer ScienceCPGSPremium Research StudentshipStudent AdministrationTeachingOverviewPart IAPart IBPart IIMasters coursesOverviewInduction for M.Phil and Part III studentsACS FormsPart III and ACS projectsPhD studentsFreshersCourses 2019–20OverviewPart IA CST 75%Part IA CST 50%Part IA NSTPart IB CST 75%Part IB CST 50%Part II CST 75%Part II CST 50%Part IIIMPhil ACSLecturer indexInstructions for lecturersCourses 2020–21OverviewPart IA CSTPart IB CST 75%Part IB CST 50%Part II CST 75%Part II CST 50%Part IIIMPhil ACSLecturer indexInstructions for lecturersExamsOverviewExamination datesExamination resultsExaminers' reportsPlagiarism and collusionPurchase of calculatorsData Retention PolicyPast exam papersGuidance on deadlinesPart III AssessmentMPhil AssessmentStudent Complaint ProcedureLecture timetablesOverviewShort form timetableSupervisionsOverviewPart II supervisions overviewPart II sign-up datesNotes on supervisingSupervisor supportAcademic exchangesOverviewAdvice for students visiting CambridgeUROP internshipsPart IB group projectsOverviewTimetablePhotosPrevious yearsPart II projectsOverviewBriefing document (Pink Book)Important datesOverseersPhase 1 reportBack-up adviceResources DeclarationStudies Involving Human ParticipantsFailure to submit proposalSelection TipsDeclaration of originalitySubmission of dissertationIP ownershipDiploma model projectsOlder project suggestionsSupervising NotesOverseer Briefing NotesDirectors of StudiesResourcesOverviewManaged Cluster ServicePart III and MPhil machinesOnline servicesInstalling LinuxMATLABMicrosoft Azure for Education MembershipMiscellaneousOverviewNewsHonoursObituariesOverviewNeil Wiseman, 1934–1995Roger Needham, 1935–2003David Wheeler, 1927–2004Karen Spärck Jones, 1935–2007Judith Ann Bailey, 1934–2008Robin Milner, 1934–2010Sir Maurice Wilkes, 1913–2010Michael JC Gordon, 1948–2017Richard Gibbens, 1962–2018Internal informationOverviewNew arrivalsOverviewAn introduction to our computing facilitiesInformation for new PhD studentsInformation for new staffInformation for visitorsInformation for hosts of visitorsGeneral informationInduction GuidelinesSpecialist resourcesSystem administrationOverviewEmailPrinting and scanningFilespaceThe CL networkSSH access to the CL systemsSupported platformsGeneric Unix/Linux informationWeb servers and sitesThe RT ticketing systemSpecialist resourcesLecture theatre AVSitemapFrequently asked questionsRoles and responsibilitiesOverviewPeopleHistoryInformation for staffOverviewAccountingParkingCyclingDepartmental policiesInformation for hosts of visitorsMeeting roomsPersonnel informationReceptionStaff trainingStoresUROP internshipsWiseman prizeHealth and safetyOverviewEmergencyFirst aidGeneral health and safetyEnvironmentFitnessH&S policies & committeesRisk assessmentLaser safetyUseful linksIndex of Health & Safety pagesCommitteePhD resourcesOverviewInductionPhD supervisorsGraduate AdvisersCPGSFirst Year Report: PhD ProposalSecond Year Report: Dissertation ScheduleThird Year Report: Progress StatementFourth Year Report: the last yearPapers and conferencesWriting upThesis formattingSubmitting your dissertationExemption from University Composition FeesLeave to work away, holidays and intermissionResearcher DevelopmentApplication deadlinesList of PhD thesisGraduate Students' ForumPAT, recycling and Building ServicesTypographic resourcesOverviewThesis formattingPreparing Tripos exam questions in LaTeXTeaching resourcesOverviewInformation for CST examinersInformation for Directors of StudiesACS module definitionProviding advice to incoming ACS studentsACS interviewing and admissionsOutreach materialCommitteesOverviewFaculty BoardDegree CommitteeGraduate EducationTripos ManagementOutreachHealth & SafetyIT StrategyEquality and DiversityResearch StaffStaff–StudentDirectors of StudiesWorkloadWellbeingGraduate StudentsEthicsBuildings and EnvironmentSelectionExternalDiscontinued committeesWilliam Gates BuildingOverviewBuilding ServicesAccess and securityCare of the WGBFacilities in officesEnergy & EnvironmentMeeting roomsStoresWest Cambridge SiteLeaving the department
Web server privacy policyComputer LaboratoryThe departmentResearchAdmissionsTeachingMiscellaneousInternal information
Privacy policy for the Computer Laboratory web server
As is the case with most web sites, our web servers
www.cl.cam.ac.uk and www.cst.cam.ac.uk
produce log files that record, for each HTTP request, the IP address
from where our servers believe the request came from (which is often
the address of an intermediate proxy server), the date and time, the
HTTP request itself (command and URL), our server's result code, and
the number of bytes transmitted. If a user has logged into one of our
web services, we may also record that user's identity. Such logins may
be verified via the University of
Cambridge Raven authentication
service. We may enable the recording of additional data from time to
time as the need arises.
All data is available to the server's administrators and will be
used primarily to monitor the server's performance, to optimize the
content of our web site, and to detect malfunctions or malicious
behaviour. Log files may also be made available to other members of
the department or the University Information Services (UIS), for
similar purposes and for use in research projects. We may keep our log
files indefinitely. Our detailed log files are not normally available
to anyone outside our department or the UIS, unless we are required to
transfer such data by UK law. We may publish summary statistics
generated from our web-server logs, which do not contain information
related to individual users.
Our sites may store HTTP cookies in your web browser as part of
user authentication (login) and to store information needed by other
facilities.
Our sites may store HTTP cookies in your web browser as used by
Google Analytics.
As is the case with most web sites, individual pages on our sites
may contain links to images on other web sites. If your web browser is
configured to fetch images automatically, similar data may be recorded
by these other web servers as well, as the images are being loaded.
Individual pages on our web sites may contain forms for interacting
with databases and other interactive services. Any data entered into
such forms may be recorded by the respective server and, where
personal data is collected, we ask the operator of such a service to
provide a link to a privacy policy for this service.
The Department regularly uses names, research profiles and
photographs of present and past students, staff, visitors and
collaborators on publicly accessible webpages available on our
websites www.cl.cam.ac.uk
and www.cst.cam.ac.uk. If you do not wish for some or all
of your details to be included, please contact the Department using
the following email address:
[Javascript required], naming
the members of staff with whom you have worked.
© 2019 Department of Computer Science and Technology, University of CambridgeInformation provided by [Javascript required]
Spotlight on...
About research at Cambridge
